









### **About Me**

As a Frontend Developer with 2+ years of experience in web development, I specialize in implementing and designing user interfaces. I possess strong skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and ReactJS, with a focus on building user-friendly websites. I am actively seeking new opportunities to further enhance my frontend expertise and contribute to impactful projects.



## **Education & Certification**

### **Education**

**Developer Courses** 

Jan 2021-Aug 2022

Department: CS50 Harvard Online/ W3C/Online Courses

Specialization: Self-studied and completed in JavaScript, ReactJs, HTML, CSS

Bach Khoa Ha Noi University

July 2022-Aug 2024

Department: Computer Science

Specialization: Software Engineering

GPA: 3.61/4.0

## Certification

TOEIC

Nov 2021-Now 2023

Total: 755

Computer Science

Listening: 390 Reading: 365



## **Skills**

Technical skills - Proficent in using JavaScript,
ReactJS,HTML,Redux
- Ability to create mobile-friendly responsive

- Ability to create mobile-friendly, responsive web pages with style SASS, SCSS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS...

- Proficent in using Word, Excel and PPT

#### Technical skills

- Familiar ExpressJS, Mongodb.
- Experienced wit GitHub, VSC, SQL, MySQL
- Working knowledge in Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)
- Familiar in working with Figma, Diagrams.net (draw.io), UML, Astash
- Agile Development and Process



# **Work Experience**

#### DATA INSIGHT TECHNOLOGY JSC

August 2024- Now

### **Front End Developer**

My responsibility:

- Software development of web based application.
- Using Javascript manipulates the elements depending on the user interactions.
- Involving in developing HTML and Javascript for client side presentation and, data validation on the client side within the forms.
- Developed features for the website, including search functionality, and discussion forums...
- Worked with APIs to integrate third party services and functionality into web applications.

#### **VLANCER SOFTWARE**

Oct 2022- August 2024

# Front End Developer

My responsibility:

- Using Javascript manipulates the elements depending on the user interactions.
- Involving in developing HTML and Javascript for client side presentation and, data validation on the client side within the forms.
- Software development of web based application.

# **Completed Project**

## EMS Systems

- Project Description: Real-time energy, management device IOT, calculation electricity price, Net Zero , Show Measures to reduce CO2 emissions ....
  - Repository That is private project
  - Technical Used: HTML | TyperScript | Vite | Redux Toolkit | React-Router-Dom/Thingsboard IOT / Antd | Tailwindcss
  - Role in project:
- Responsible for all tasks related to the front end
- Build some functions as create show chart real-time, Export report, Import Form Data

## Solar Monitoring Systems

- Project Description: Real-time energy solar, management device IOT, calculation electricity price....
- Repository <u>That is private project</u>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | MUI | Vite | Thingsboard IOT
- Role in project:
- Antd design for Layout page
- Build some functions as create show chart realtime,

## OEE Solution Systems

- Project Description: Real-time activity of device, management device IOT, Production planning, Device control ....
- Repository <u>That is private project</u>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | CSS | Vite | Thingsboard IOT | Antd
- Role in project::
- Build style CSS layout
- Build features Chart, Overview Page,...
- Build functions as add Item, delete, calculator price total,..



# **Completed Project**



### Anime Web

- Project Description: Anime Film Web
- Repository <a href="https://anime-zeta-three.vercel.app/">https://anime-zeta-three.vercel.app/</a>
- Technical Used: HTML | SASS | SCSS
- Role in project :
- That is personal project
- Responsible for all tasks related to the front end

### Admin Dashboard

- Project Description: Admin dashboard energy systems
- Repository <a href="https://ems-frontend-pearl.vercel.app/">https://ems-frontend-pearl.vercel.app/</a>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | MUI | Vite |
- Role in project:
- Antd design for Layout page
- Responsible for all tasks related to the front end

# Online Shopping

- Project Description: Shopping ecommerce
- Repository <u>https://ecomerce-beta-one.vercel.app</u>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | CSS| Vite | React-Router-Dom
- Role in project::
- Build style CSS layout Cart
- Build features Cart Shopping, Button Add Cart...
- Build functions as add Item, delete, calculator price total,..

# **Completed Project**



## Quizz App

- Project Description: Quizz Game
- Repository <u>https://react-quizz-app-seven.vercel.app/</u>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | MUI | Vite | Redux Toolkit |React-Router-Dom
- Role in project :
- Create Dashboard Page, Question Page, Score page, Validate Form
- Redux for actions choose question, answer,...
  - Deloy demo project

#### Trello Clone

- Project Description: Drag and Drop Web
- Repository <a href="https://react-trello-web.vercel.app/">https://react-trello-web.vercel.app/</a>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | MUI | Vite |
- Role in project:
- Antd design for Layout page
- Build features List, Card list, Drag and Drop Card
- Build some functions as create new card, delete card

# **Shopping Cart**

- Project Description: Shopping Order UI
- Repository <u>https://shopping-cartss.vercel.app/</u>
- Technical Used: HTML | ReactJS | CSS| Vite | React-Router-Dom
- Role in project: :
- Build style CSS layout Cart
- Build features Cart Shopping, Button Add Cart...
- Build functions as add Item, delete, calculator price total,..